mapnation.com 2009-06-19

# MapNation

**MapNation.com Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy explains how MapNation.com. ("MapNation") collects and uses your personal information that you submit to us online. MapNation reserves the right to modify the terms of this policy at any time. Such modifications shall become effective immediately upon posting or, depending on the type of change, by notifying you by email. Your continued use of, or registration with, this website shall constitute your acceptance of these terms. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy, in whole or in part, you are not authorized to use this website and should terminate registration by following the opt-out instructions or sending an email to unsubscribe@MapNation.com . For questions about our policy, please submit your request in writing to privacy@MapNation.com . 

What we may collect:   
MapNation only collects personal information which you provide in response to specific information requests on this website and MapNation's affiliated online properties. This information may include name, address, phone number and email address. In addition, we may collect your IP address and other information through the use of electronic "cookies." 

How we may use your information:   
By registering with MapNation, you consent to the collection, processing, and transfer of your personal information in accordance with this policy. MapNation may use your information a) for the purpose for which it was collected, b) as disclosed at the time such information is provided to us, c) to protect the rights or property of MapNation, its affiliated online properties, and other registrants of MapNation websites, and d) as required by law. We may also share your personal information with our partners, advertisers, service providers, affiliates, and other third parties that we believe can provide you with special offers and opportunities. MapNation carefully screens the parties with whom it contracts but makes no guarantee about their use and protection of your personal information or failure to abide by our privacy policy. Where MapNation or our affiliated online properties link to other websites, MapNation is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those websites. 

Security:   
MapNation regularly monitors this website, its affiliated websites, and databases for fraud, abuse, and unauthorized use of information to protect your personal information that is under our control. 

Do Not Call Registry Compliance:   
By submitting personal contact and/or financial information to MapNation through this website or any of its affiliated online properties, you hereby grant written permission to MapNation, its affiliated websites, and its business partners to contact you by telephone, mail, and/or e-mail. Further, by registering with MapNation through this website or any of its affiliated online properties you are consenting to receive phone calls from MapNation, its affiliated websites, and its business partners for contact via telephone, including but not limited to lenders that may contact you regarding credit counseling and thereby registrants waive their right to file a claim with the FTC or any other agency in reference to these calls or contacts. 

Opt-Out Opportunity:   
MapNation registrants may opt-out of receiving further communications from MapNation at any time by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in any MapNation e-mail received by registrant or by clicking the unsubscribe link [here](http://www.dnelist.com/u/bf8b8e295c02747ddb9ced3b2555415115). Please note that unsubscribing from one email list does not automatically unsubscribe you from any other email list that you may be on. Please read the email carefully to find out which list you are unsubscribing from.

Children's Privacy:   
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract or intended for anyone under 18 years of age. 

Assignment:   
In its sole discretion, MapNation may transfer, sell or assign your personal information collected on and through this website and affiliated online properties to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of MapNation and/or its affiliated online properties. 

*The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on or about November 16, 2006.
